# London, United Kingdom

## **Edward Brodski** brodskiedward@gmail.com Frontend-Centric Full Stack Developer

linkedin.com/in/edward-brodski www.edwardbrodski.com

Passionate Software Engineer and Project Manager with 7+ years of programming experience, 2+ years of work experience and a Master's degree in Computer Science.

Areas of expertise: Python Scripting, Frontend, Workflow design and Task Management.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Project Manager** Jun 2022 — Sep 2022 NDB Remote

- Led the design team in optimizing workflows and task descriptions, ensuring seamless project execution from concept to implementation
- · Administered community resources and spearheaded the development of custom Discord and Telegram bots, enhancing marketing outreach and community engagement.
- Led the restructuring of the Kanban system, replacing irrelevant tasks with current, actionable items to align with business goals.
- Conducted comprehensive evaluations of completed work, scrutinizing user interaction, security, and performance to uphold high-quality standards.

**Frontend Developer** Aug 2020 — Feb 2022

OptimumSoftware Remote

- · Specialized in front-end development using React: crafted a custom UI library, designed input interfaces, and optimized cross-device scaling to ensure responsive and consistent user experiences.
- Collaborated in the expansion of the internal GraphQL API systems, adding new queries to support evolving application needs.
- Worked with designers to refine the quality and presentation of information across multiple web platforms.

#### **PROJECTS**

#### Context-Free-Grammar Equivalence Research Project, Python, NumPy, Pandas

Jun 2021 — May 2022

- Produced the first Open Source implementation of a state-of-the-art algorithm for evaluating grammar equivalence.
- Developed testing methods for the evaluation of different approaches presented by other works as well as my own.

#### Personalized Finance Assistant, Python, Pandas, Tk

Aug 2022 — Jul 2023

- Developed infrastructure to ingest and unify different transaction streams into a single database.
- Implemented an integrated labelling and tagging system.
- Designed and produced a GUI application for the classification and analysis of data providing an integrated view of graphics and tables.

#### **Intelligent Early Wildfire Detection,** Python, Pandas, PyTorch

Sep 2022 — Jun 2023

- Researched Wildfire smoke patterns and developed as system for automatically generating fire patterns for AI training and testing.
- Carried out Data Analysis and validation for the generated datasets.
- Trained a final model which reached an accuracy of 96.72%.

#### Snake Evolution, Python

Mar 2019 — Oct 2020

- Designed a flexible grid based ecosystem with a graphical output.
- Developed a gene system and offspring gene randomization for the snakes.
- Added data analyzation systems such as live graphs and decision visualizations.

### **EDUCATION**

MSci Computer Science — First-Class, Queen Mary University of London

Sep 2019 — Jul 2023

**Senior School,** Millfield, Computer Science  $-A^*$ , Further Mathematics -A, Mathematics  $-A^*$ , Physics -A

Sep 2017 — Jun 2019

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, TypeScript, JavaScript, C++, Java **Programming Languages** 

**Technologies** NodeJS, React, React-Native, HTML, CSS, NumPy, Pandas, PyTorch, REST, GraphQL, AWS

Git, GitHub, Linux, Docker, Fusion 360, Jira, Figma, ClickUp **Tools** 

**Additional Courses** MHFA(Mental Health First Aid) England Completed in Jan 2023